(a large building with a lot of lights on it)
Dans le monde de la magie, tout ce qui disparaît réapparaît.
(a black and white photo of a window with a light shining through it)
Oh ! Ah, ça fait du bien de savoir !
(a man in a suit is standing in the dark)
(a couple of people standing next to each other people)
Oh ! Ah, ça fait du bien de savoir !
(a woman in a black dress standing in the dark)
Montez, vous serez notre assistant !
(two people on stage)
(three men in suits on stage)
Montez, vous serez notre assistant !
Ok ! Disparition dans 3...
(a man in a hoodie standing in the dark)
2... 1...
(a man in a hoodie standing in front of a crowd)
Daniel Atlas pour vous servir. Alors, qui veut voir un tour de magie ?
(a man in a black hoodie is standing on stage)
(the logo for the group m6)
Daniel Atlas pour vous servir. Alors, qui veut voir un tour de magie ?
(the title for the movie lioncat)
Je pense que les cavaliers auraient été fiers de nous. Mon Atlas était... parfait.
(a woman is sitting on a couch and laughing)
(a man sitting down)
Je pense que les cavaliers auraient été fiers de nous. Mon Atlas était... parfait.
Ah ouais ? Ça, c'est à moi d'en juger.
(a man standing in a dark room with a light on)
Oh !
(a man and woman sitting on a couch)
(a person holding a cell phone in front of a pile of money)
Oh !
D'après cette carte, bizarrement, j'ai besoin de vous.
(a woman in a black dress sitting on a couch)
(a man in a black jacket is staring at something)
D'après cette carte, bizarrement, j'ai besoin de vous.
(a man in a black shirt is looking at the camera)
Pourquoi pas les autres cavaliers ?
(a man in a black jacket is looking at his cell)
Les autres cavaliers sont morts.
(a couple sitting on a couch in a room)
Oh non, c'est pas vrai.
(a man in a black jacket looking at a woman)
Non, non, ils sont morts pour moi. C'était trop intense pour eux. Ils sont partis. Arrêtez de m'interrompre.
(a man and woman sitting in a bar)
(a clock with a star on it)
Non, non, ils sont morts pour moi. C'était trop intense pour eux. Ils sont partis. Arrêtez de m'interrompre.
Je vous parle du tour de magie le plus énorme et le plus stylé que vous ayez jamais vu.
(a man standing in a dark room with a light on)
C'est maintenant ou jamais.
(a man and woman standing in front of a mirror)
C'est quoi le tour ?
(a man in a black jacket standing in front of a mirror)
Le diamanteur. Le joyau le plus cher de l'histoire.
(a video of a city with a lot of buildings)
(a diamond is shown in this still - unseen video)
Le diamanteur. Le joyau le plus cher de l'histoire.
(a large statue in the middle of a square)
Il a quoi de si spécial, ce diamant ?
(a man walking down a street next to a statue)
C'est parce que c'est un tarot magique qu'il a dit.
(a person is cutting a piece of red fabric)
Ça fait des décennies que les Vanderberg vendent des diamants au chef de guerre.
(a couple walking down a staircase in a building)
(a woman in a dress holding a glass)
Ça fait des décennies que les Vanderberg vendent des diamants au chef de guerre.
(a car driving through the desert)
Au marchand d'armes, au trafiquant, pour les aider à faire leur blanchiment.
(a man in a suit and tie walking with a suitcase)
(a large group of people standing in front of a tunnel)
Au marchand d'armes, au trafiquant, pour les aider à faire leur blanchiment.
(a woman in a white coat talking to a man in a suit)
(canon eos)
On n'arrête pas le diable en lui coupant les mains, mais en lui piquant son portefeuille.
(a man and woman dancing in a room)
(a white light shining in the sky)
On n'arrête pas le diable en lui coupant les mains, mais en lui piquant son portefeuille.
(a man in a tuxed)
Césame, ouvre-toi.
(a woman in a silver dress standing next to a glass box)
(a group of people standing in front of a building)
(a woman in a silver dress standing next to a man in a suit)
Il est toujours entre de bonnes mains.
(a woman in a dress dancing with people)
Du calme.
(a man in a tuxed)
Les diamants sont éternels.
Arrêtez-le !
(a man in a tuxed)
(a man in a suit and tie walking down a hallway)
Jack, qu'est-ce que tu fais là ?
(a man and woman dancing in a room)
(a man in a white shirt is dancing)
Jack, qu'est-ce que tu fais là ?
Je viens de sauver.
(a man in a white shirt is dancing)
(a woman in a dress is walking down a hallway)
Enler Reeves !
(a group of people standing around a room)
Plus tard, le fan club.
(a man and woman standing in a room)
(a man in a tuxed)
Salut les gars !
(a man and woman standing in a room)
Salut !
Et vous êtes qui ?
(a man in a tuxed suit and bow tie)
Vous.
(a group of people standing around a man in a suit)
Allez, on y va !
(a car is driving down the street at night)
(a train car is parked on a bridge)
(a group of people walking through a field)
Mes cavaliers.
(a man in a suit and tie walking through a room)
Adéus !
Vous avez été réunis dans un but précis.
(two men in suits and hats are talking)
Les bonbons font leur effet.
(a man in a hat and black jacket)
(a man in a suit and hat standing in a room)
Les bonbons font leur effet.
(a large group of people standing in a cave)
Faire tomber deux générations de criminels en un tour de passe-passe.
(a group of people in a room with a piano)
(a man in a suit is standing in front of a fire)
Faire tomber deux générations de criminels en un tour de passe-passe.
(a man in a room with a door open)
(a woman in a white dress is dancing)
Faire tomber deux générations de criminels en un tour de passe-passe.
Huit magiciens contre un réseau criminel international.
(a man and woman sitting next to each other people)
(a group of people sitting around a table)
Huit magiciens contre un réseau criminel international.
(a woman standing in a elevator)
(a group of people standing around a woman)
On a toutes nos chances.
(a man in a hat and coat standing next to a fire)
(the title for the movie zombie)
(a car driving down a dirt road in the middle of a field)
(a man standing in a doorway with a dog)
Vous voulez voir un tour de magie ?
(a man in a red coat walking down a hallway)
Adéus !
(need for speed - the game)
Le spectacle vous plaît ?
(a man and woman standing next to each other people)
On peut passer aux choses sérieuses.
(a woman in a suit and tie standing next to a man in a suit)
(a blur of a red car driving through a forest)
On peut passer aux choses sérieuses.
(a man in a suit is dancing on a floor)
(a woman in a black jacket is standing in an office)
(a man in a suit is standing in front of a mirror)
(harry and hermik in the library)
C'est un cul-de-sac, les gars.
(a man in a hat and a suit is standing in a hallway)
Césame, ouvre-toi.
(a man in a suit and hat standing next to a bookcase)
(a man in a hat and a woman in a dress)
T'as raison, on lâche rien à mérite.
(a man in a suit and hat standing next to a bookcase)
Ça se tentait, hein ?
(a man in a suit and hat standing next to a woman)
Sérieux ?
On sait jamais.
(a man in a suit and hat standing next to a woman)
(a man in a suit and hat standing next to another man)
Cécile, là, je crois que tu serais.
(a man in a suit and hat standing in front of a bookcase)
On va.
(the title for the film inssables 3)
(a red and white background with the words vous)